[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Let's train the sentiment classifier.
现在让我们来训练这个顾客情感分类器
And we're gonna do this in two steps.
我们将会分两步来实现这个分类器
First, we're gonna do a train test split of the data.
第一步，我们将原始数据划分为训练集和测试集
So I'm gonna compute the training data.
我现在要编程获取训练集数据
We're gonna split the data into training data.
我们把数据划分为训练集数据和测试集数据
And test data just like we talked in the regression class and
就像我们之前在回归的课上做的那样
just like we did in the regression notebook.
划分的方法也与之前在回归模型中用到的指令相似
So we're gonna use, we'll take this product table.
我们需要使用之前导入的商品信息表
Products.
输入“Products”
And then we're going to do the random split.
我们进行的是随机划分
So, oops.
因此
Products.
输入“Products”
And then we're gonna do that random split,
输入“random split”指令进行随机划分
where we're gonna do 80% for training, 20% for testing.
80%的数据作为训练集，而20%的数据作为测试集
And just so that you can reproduce this at home, I'm gonna do the seed = 0.
你可以在家完成这个重新划分数据的操作，设置“seed = 0”
Just like we discussed in regression.
就像我们之前在回归课上讨论的那样
Normally you wouldn't do this, you pick another random seed, but
通常你可以不必进行这样的操作，你可以选择其他随机种子
I wanted the random seed to be the same,
但是我想要获得相同的随机种子
so when you do it, you get exactly the same results I did.
如果你输入这样的指令，就可以获得和我一样的结果
So this is my first step, train test split on this data set, and now we're ready.
这就是我们的第一步，从数据中划分出训练集，现在我们已经完成了
We're gonna build that famous sentiment model.
然后我们建立那个著名的顾客情感分类模型
And here, we're going to use graphlab and
这里用到了“graphlab”库
we're going to use a particular classifier called the logistic classifier.
然后用到了一个特定的分类器——逻辑回归分类器
And in the course on classification,
这门课所涉及到分类的内容
we're going to learn a lot about different kinds of classifiers like logistic
我们会学到很多像逻辑回归一样的不同分类算法
regression, this one, support vector machines Decision trees and others.
比如支持向量机，决策树等
But let's start with just a logistic classifier.
但是，我们首先还是从逻辑回归分类器开始
And just like in you can type .create after the name and
你可以在名字后面键入“.create”
it'll actually create the classifier for you.
就可以创建这样的分类器
And as input, it takes us a few parameters.
然后需要几个输入参数
So we're gonna take the train data, as one parameter.
训练集数据是第一个参数
Then we're gonna see that the target,
第二个参数是“target”
the thing we're trying to classify, is the sentiment column.
我们要分类的东西是数据表中的情感列
And then we're gonna have to tell it what features to use.
我们需要指定使用什么样的特征
So for the features we're going to use just the word count column.
我们用的特征就是“word count"列
So this is the new column that we've created above for word count.
这一个新数据列是我们上面为“word count”所创建的
And, I'm going to give that a validation set.
然后我们还需要设置验证集validation set
So the validation set is going to be my test_data.
验证集就是我们的测试数据
So validation_set=test_data.
因此我们让 “validation_set = test_data”
Okay.
好
So now we execute the cell.
现在我们开始计算这个单元
And we shall be a building a sentiment classifier model.
来建立一个情感分类器模型
And we're only gonna take a few seconds, and here we go.
我们只需要等待几秒钟，模型就训练好了
It's done.
完成！
And you will see [INAUDIBLE] the data, and
从数据中你可以发现
the validation accuracy as it goes along it seems to be getting better and better.
精确度是逐渐变好的
But let's actually do a peer evaluation.
然后让我们来做一下互评吧
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community